A Finding Aid to the American Federation of Arts Records, 1895-1993 (bulk 1909-1969), in the Archives of American Art AAA.amerfeda
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1934-1969; Series 5; (boxes 17-78)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Exhibitions, 1961-1964; 5.17
    - NY-8: Major Works in Minor Scale, 1962-1963 (Box 75)
    - NY-9: Prints by Great Masters, 1962-1963 (Box 75)
    - NY-10: Forty Artists Under Forty, 1961-1963 (Box 75)
    - NY-11: Contemporary Landscapes and Their Antecedents, 1962 (Box 75)
    - NY-12: Japanese Prints, 1962-1963 (Box 76)
    - NY-13: American Silver, 1963-1966 (Box 76)
    - NY-14: The Paper on the Wall, 1963-1964 (Box 76)
    - NY-15: American Hardware, 1963-1964 (Box 76)
    - NY-16: American Impressionism, 1965-1967 (Box 76)
    - NY-17: Modern Realism and Surrealism, 1965-1967 (Box 76)
    - NY-18: The Figure International, 1965-1966 (Box 76)
    - NY-19: The Ash Can School, 1966-1967, nd (Box 76)
    - NY-20: On Paper, 1966-1967 (Box 76)
    - NY-21: The Master Artist, 1967-1968 (Box 76)
  - Rejected Exhibitions, 1961-1968; 5.18
    - America's Many Faces, 1961-1962 (Box 76)
    - Rejects, General, 1961-1963 (Box 77)
    - Hogarth, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Early Architecture of Quebec, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Folk Art, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Color, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Architecture of Masonry, 1964 (Box 77)
    - American Republic Insurance Company, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Carola Torres Tapestries, 1965 (Box 77)
    - CHEI, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Children's Drawings, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Colorado University Travel Project, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Commissioned Sculpture, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Design of a City-Foster City, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Old Master Drawings-Bergamo, Italy, 1965-1966 (Box 77)
    - Allston Collection of Italian Painting, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Architecture in America, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Colonial Art in Latin America- Tuscon, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Drawing Society- South American Tour, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Painters Under 35, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Fantasy Furniture MOCC, 1966 (Box 77)
    - First Intercollegiate Student Exhibition, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Contemporary Greek Painting, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Hirshhorn, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Historical Engravings, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Hungarian Art, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Visual Poetry-The History of American Porcelain, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Peter Fink-Photography Show, 1966-1967 (Box 77)
    - E.B. Crocker Gallery-Old Master Drawings, 1966-1967 (Box 77)
    - Kahlil Gibran-Telfair, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Hi-Way Culture-Man at the Wheel, 1967 (Box 77)
    - How Art Books Are Produced, 1967 (Box 77)
    - America-Israel Cultural House, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Folk Crafts from North India, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Mary Cassatt, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Dance in Contemporary American Indian Art, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Jean Dubuffet, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Faculty Artists, 1968 (Box 77)
    - Dance, undated (Box 77)
  - Suggested Exhibitions, 1964-1967; 5.19
    - Tunhang Cave Paintings, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Walters Art Gallery, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Glory, Jest and Riddle, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Self-Portraits, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Rosenwald, 1964 (Box 77)
    - School Program, 1964 (Box 77)
    - New Zealand, 1964-1966 (Box 77)
    - School of Paris, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Spode, 1965 (Box 77)
    - South African National Gallery, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Joe and Emily Lowe Art Gallery, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Japanese Painting, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Indian Painting, 1965 (Box 77)
    - IGAS Prints, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Primitive Art-UCLA (Box 77)
    - Swedish Painting, 1965-1966 (Box 77)
    - The Sculptors' Guild, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Ezra Stoller, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Made with Paper, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Modern Chinese Prints and Paintings, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Schueler Exhibition, 1966 (Box 77)
    - The Grand Design-L'Enfant Plan, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Portugal, 1966 (Box 77)
    - John Stewart Curry, 1966 (Box 77)
    - La Scala Theater Design, 1966 (Box 77)
    - WPA-University of Maryland, 1966 (Box 77)
    - 20th National Exhibition of Prints-Library of Congress, 1966 (Box 77)
    - India-Arts and Crafts, 1966-1967 (Box 77)
    - Ornamental Pen Drawings, 1966-1967 (Box 77)
    - Religion in Art Today, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Salon d'Antomne, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Salishan, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Contemporary Russian Painting, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Southern Sculpture, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Contemporary Malaysian Art, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Religious Architecture, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Cross Section of Contemporary Graphics, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Japanese Scrolls, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Sullivan, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Copenhagen, 1967 (Box 77)
    - Swiss Engravers, 1967-1968 (Box 77)
    - Makende Sculpture, 1968 (Box 77)
    - Thailand, undated (Box 77)
    - Magic Realism, undated (Box 77)
    - Sculpture, undated (Box 77)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Exhibition Installations, 1951-1955; undated; 5.20
    - Photographs of India, Japan, Manila, Venice, and Berlin, 1951, 1955, undated (Box 78)
    - Photographs of Domestic Shows, 1951, 1955, undated (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous Installations, undated (Box 78)
    - Installation Views of Exhibitions, undated (Box 78)
    - Various Exhibitions, undated (Box 78)
- Printed Material, 1990-1993; Series 6; (boxes 78)
  - Media Arts Program, 1990-1991 (Box 78)
  - Exhibition Programs, 1990-1994 (Box 78)
  - Memos to Members, 1991-1993 (Box 78)
  - News Releases, 1990-1993 (Box 78)
  - Newsletters, 1990-1993 (Box 78)
  - Annual Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 78)
  - Lantern Slides from "New Horizons in America" Lecture Series, undated (Box 78)
- Miscellaneous Files, undated; 1926-1962; Series 7; (boxes 79)
  - Architectural League of New York Records Relating to National Award Programs, 1926-1962 (Box 79 (pam))
- Oversized Material, undated; 1890s; Series 8; (boxes 80-85)
  - AFA's Portfolio No. 1, "American Artists in Color Reproduction," (also includes one silkscreen print) (Box OV 80)
  - 19th-Century Magazines, late 1800s (Box OV 81-84)
  - Dada Poster, undated (Box OV 85)
  - Henri Cartier-Bresson Poster, undated (Box OV 85)